# CHRISTOPHER PFAFF

3600 SOUTH LAMAR BLVD, AUSTIN, TX 78704

7165232185 | chrispfaff10@gmail.com

- www.github.com/chrisPfaff
- www.christopherpfaff.com
- www.codepen.io/ChrisPfaff10

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Looking for an entry-level position to help grow a companies web presence. Web developer offering advanced knowledge of HTML/CSS and JavaScript, as well as experience with Frameworks like React and Angular. Creative, outside-the-box thinker with one year UX/UI design experience. Adept at conceptualizing unconventional solutions to complex problems.

### **SKILLS**

- HTML
- JavaScript
- CSS
- SCSS
- Node.js
- Express
- Ajax
- Jquery
- React
- Angular.js
- Mongodb/mongoose
- API design knowledge
- Knowledge of ADA compliance

- Self-starter
- Focused
- Innovative thinker
- Detail-oriented
- Strong communication skills
- Patient

# WORK HISTORY

#### **MYSELF**

Freelance Web/Software Developer | Youngstown, New York | September 2017 - Current

- Wrote Javascript applications in React/Express architecture.
- Identified and suggested new technologies and tools for enhancing product value and increasing team productivity.
- Designed intuitive graphical user interfaces using knowledge of serial communications and database design.

- Analyzed and designed relational databases using MongoDB.
- Made HTML and CSS landing pages with functional JavaScript.
- Monitored and updated back-end data by inter-communicating between Node.js and the front end.

#### **H2GROW**

Production Worker | Lewiston, New York | August 2004 - February 2005

- Received and correctly processed both written and verbal instructions, prints and work orders.
- Built containers and pack parts in accordance with detailed packing specifications.
- Expertly assembled millwork products such as doors, windows, cabinets and counters.
- Ran stainless, aluminum, steel and PVC piping.
- Correctly and safely used a variety of hand tools, saws and cutting equipment to carry out job duties.

#### **ONTARIO HOUSE**

Bartender/ Manager | Youngstown, NY | July 2006 - Current

- Greeted guests in a timely and professional manner.
- Received beverage orders from wait staff and delivered beverages to guests.
- Enthusiastically and appealingly described food and drink specials to guests.
- Poured drinks using standard pour according to specifications.
- Managed bar revenues, ensuring that all patrons were billed and all cash properly accounted for.
- Closed out cash register and prepared cashier report.
- Changed beer kegs.
- 10 years bartending experience.

#### **SCOTPC**

Computer Repair Assistant | Ransomville , New York | July 2014 - May 2015

- Resolved computer hardware and software, printing, installation, word processing, email and operating systems issues.
- Restored data, operating systems, files, documents, and drivers.
- Installed software and operating systems on numerous company computers.
- Resolved virus and malware issues at a successful rate.
- Repaired and replaced hardware, including ram, motherboards, video cards.

#### **EDUCATION**

Hack Reactor - Software/Web Development

Hack Reactor Prep-Course - Javascript/Web Development

FullStack Academy Prep-Course - Javascript/Web Development

Erie Community College - Information Technology

Niagara Community College - Criminal Justice